A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1441)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1442)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1443)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Original Manuscript, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1444)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Reprints, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1445)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Reprints, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1446)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Reprints, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1447)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Reprints, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1448)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1449)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1450)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1451)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1452)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1453)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Original Manuscript, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1454)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Reprints, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1455)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Reprints, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1456)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Reprints, 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1457)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:67, 1983 July 22 (Box 577, Folder 1458)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1459)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1460)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1461)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1462)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Original Manuscript, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1463)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Reprints, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1464)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Reprints, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1465)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Reprints, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1466)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1467)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1468)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1469)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Sources: "Check Copy"25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1470)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Original Manuscript, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1471)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Reprints, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1472)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Reprints, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1473)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1474)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1475)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1476)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1477)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Original Manuscript, 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1478)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Reprints, 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1479)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Reprints, 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1480)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:72, 1983 August 5 (Box 580, Folder 1481)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1482)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1483)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1484)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Original Manuscript, 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1485)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Reprints, 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1486)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Reprints, 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1487)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction" Reprints, 25:73, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 581, Folder 1488)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1489)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1490)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1491)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Original Manuscript, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1492)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Reprints, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1493)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Reprints, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1494)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Reprints, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1495)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Reprints, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1496)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 582, Folder 1497)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Rabies Surveillance CDC, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1498)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Rabies Surveillance CDC, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1499)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent" Rabies Surveillance CDC, 25:77, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1500)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1501)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1502)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1503)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Original Manuscript, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1504)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Reprints, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1505)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Reprints, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1506)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:78, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 583, Folder 1507)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:80, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 584, Folder 1508)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:80, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 584, Folder 1509)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:80, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 584, Folder 1510)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Original Manuscript, 25:80, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 584, Folder 1511)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Reprints, 25:80, 1983 Aug. 19 (Box 584, Folder 1512)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:80, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1513)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1514)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1515)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1516)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Manufacturers? Replies, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1517)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Original Manuscript, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1518)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 584, Folder 1519)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 585, Folder 1520)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 585, Folder 1521)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 585, Folder 1522)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 585, Folder 1523)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 2 (Box 585, Folder 1524)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy" Reprints, 25:81, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 585, Folder 1525)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1526)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1526)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1527)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1527)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Original Manuscript, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1528)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1528)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Reprints, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1529)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1529)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Reprints, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1530)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1530)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Reprints, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1531)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 16 (Box 586, Folder 1531)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions" Reprints, 25:85, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 586, Folder 1532)
  - "Dosage of naloxone" 25:108, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 586, Folder 1532)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1533)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1534)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Original Manuscript, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1535)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Reprints, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1536)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Reprints, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1537)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:89, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1538)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1539)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 587, Folder 1540)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1541)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Original Manuscript, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1542)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Reprints, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1543)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:90, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1544)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:91, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1545)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:91, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1546)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:91, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1547)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Original Manuscript, 25:91, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1548)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Reprints, 25:91, 1983 Sept. 30 (Box 588, Folder 1549)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:91, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 588, Folder 1550)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 588, Folder 1551)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1552)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Sources: "Check Copy", 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1553)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Original Manuscript, 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1554)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Reprints, 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1555)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:93, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1556)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:95, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1557)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:95, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1558)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Sources: "Check Copy", 25:95, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1559)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Original Manuscript, 25:95, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1560)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Reprints, 25:95, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 589, Folder 1561)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug" Reprints, 25:95, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1562)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1563)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1564)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Sources: "Check Copy", 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1565)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Original Manuscript, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1566)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Reprints, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1567)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Reprints, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1568)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty" Reprints, 25:97, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 590, Folder 1569)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1570)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1571)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Sources: "Check Copy", 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1572)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Original Manuscript, 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1573)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Reprints, 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1574)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Reprints, 25:98, 1983 Oct. 28 (Box 591, Folder 1575)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:98, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 591, Folder 1576)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 591, Folder 1577)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1578)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1579)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Reprints, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1580)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Reprints, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1581)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Reprints, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1582)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Reprints, 25:101, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 592, Folder 1583)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:101, 1983 November 11 (Box 592, Folder 1584)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:102, 1983 November 11 (Box 592, Folder 1585)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:102, 1983 November 11 (Box 592, Folder 1586)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media" Original Manuscript, 25:102, 1983 November 11 (Box 592, Folder 1587)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media" Reprints, 25:102, 1983 November 11 (Box 593, Folder 1588)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media" Reprints, 25:102, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1589)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1590)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1591)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1592)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Original Manuscript, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1593)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1594)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 593, Folder 1595)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 594, Folder 1596)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 594, Folder 1597)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 594, Folder 1598)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 594, Folder 1599)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Reprints, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 11 (Box 594, Folder 1600)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:103, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 594, Folder 1601)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1602)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Manufacturers? Replies, 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1603)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1604)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Original Manuscript, 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1605)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Reprints, 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1606)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:105, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1607)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1608)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1609)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1610)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Original Manuscript, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1611)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Reprints, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1612)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Reprints, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 595, Folder 1613)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Reprints, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1614)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:106, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1615)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1616)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1617)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1618)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1619)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Original Manuscript, 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1620)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Reprints, 25:107, 1983 Nov. 25 (Box 596, Folder 1621)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography" Reprints, 25:107, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 596, Folder 1622)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1623)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Manufacturers' Replies, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1624)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Sources: "Check Copy" 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1625)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Original Manuscript, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1626)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Reprints, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1627)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Reprints, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1628)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Reprints, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1629)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)" Advertising: Package Insert, 25:109, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 597, Folder 1630)
- "ACETOHYDROXAMIC ACID: Oral acetohydroxamic acid (Lithostat) for- staghorn calculi" Consultants: ML Drafts, 25:110, 1983 Dec. 9 (Box 598, Folder 1631)